<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>Resources on C25Kio - Start Running </title>
    <link>http://www.c25k.io.com/resources/</link>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <author>Enthusiastic Hugo User</author>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2014, Enthusiastic Hugo User; all rights reserved.</rights>
    <updated>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 UTC</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discussions &amp; Support</title>
      <link>http://www.c25k.io.com/resources/discussion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      <author>Enthusiastic Hugo User</author>
      <guid>http://www.c25k.io.com/resources/discussion/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;some-content:1dc9c0714b072133d4c76c3091b74ddb&#34;&gt;Some Content&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some content&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspirations</title>
      <link>http://www.c25k.io.com/resources/inspiration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      <author>Enthusiastic Hugo User</author>
      <guid>http://www.c25k.io.com/resources/inspiration/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;ben-davis-120-pound-weight-loss-journey:b8483abfa47fe35ce2582e628562e321&#34;&gt;Ben Davis&amp;rsquo; 120 pound weight loss journey&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are over weight, and are considering running, watch this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;this-is-why-i-run-c25k:b8483abfa47fe35ce2582e628562e321&#34;&gt;This is why I run: C25K&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This race is my destiny. I finished C25K four years ago, now I just need to take the &amp;ldquo;5&amp;rdquo; out and run the C2K. I dream about running Coast to Kosciuszko, it&amp;rsquo;s what inspires me to run every day. Watch this space for 2012. View the trailer for &amp;ldquo;Coast to Kosciuszko: A portrait of an Ultramarathon&amp;rdquo; and be inspired.
An essay about running written by a cancer survivor
If you want to find out what running can mean to someone, read this. If you have trouble getting out of bed at any time to go for a run, remember reading this. If you&amp;rsquo;re hurting during your run and feel like stopping, remember reading this. If you ever get injured because of running, read this again. Jenny posts at the Runners World forum, she has inspired me and countless others during her battle. Thanks Jenny for letting me publish your story here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-common-question-why-do-people-drop-out-during-c25k:b8483abfa47fe35ce2582e628562e321&#34;&gt;A common question: why do people drop out during C25K?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a forum I contribute to, someone asked:&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;m interested to know if those who have started this previously and got to week 3 or 4 had to stop because of injury or it got too hard or life just got in the way?&amp;rdquo; I have also seen this sort of question in other C25K forums. Here was my reply on the forum in question.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;no-excuses:b8483abfa47fe35ce2582e628562e321&#34;&gt;No Excuses&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Great motivational piece from our friends at Nike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;darin-s-story:b8483abfa47fe35ce2582e628562e321&#34;&gt;Darin&amp;rsquo;s story&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine being told you can&amp;rsquo;t donate your kidney to your very sick daughter because of your weight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-pre-dawn-people:b8483abfa47fe35ce2582e628562e321&#34;&gt;The Pre-Dawn People&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Journalist Dana Marytin meets a running group, the pre-dawn people. This story really captures what running can bring to you life, and why you keep running years after finishing the C25K. I have two of my own &amp;ldquo;Pre-Dawn People&amp;rdquo; groups I run with, and the relationships I have made are just as close as Dana describes in this great story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;ultraruntv-ultra-running-videos:b8483abfa47fe35ce2582e628562e321&#34;&gt;UltraRunTv Ultra Running Videos&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Watch some amazing runners do amazing thngs on UltraRunTV. You may not be at this stage yet, but one day, who knows?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;books-for-inspiration:b8483abfa47fe35ce2582e628562e321&#34;&gt;Books for inspiration&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are four fantastic books I have enjoyed reading that have help inspire me to run.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcasts</title>
      <link>http://www.c25k.io.com/resources/podcasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      <author>Enthusiastic Hugo User</author>
      <guid>http://www.c25k.io.com/resources/podcasts/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;robert-ullrey-s-c25k-podcasts:490078144366c347e8b62bdc4bb6103e&#34;&gt;Robert Ullrey&amp;rsquo;s C25K Podcasts&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Robert has recorded nine podcasts to accompany you on your runs. Some great music, plus Robert will tell you when to run, and when to walk&amp;hellip;a must have.
How to add mp3 files to your iPod: First save the mp3 files to your hard disk. Then open iTunes and under “File”, go to “Add File to Library”. Browse for the file and add it. Then in iTunes add the file to your iPod.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add podcast link &amp;amp; youtube stuff&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;podrunner-intervals-first-day-to-5k-http-www-djsteveboy-com-intervals-html:490078144366c347e8b62bdc4bb6103e&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.djsteveboy.com/intervals.html&#34;&gt;Podrunner Intervals: First Day to 5K&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mixed by DJ BeatSmith, this first 27-minute set is said to be a great introduction to the world of interval training to start you on your path to a nonstop 5K run! Graham Cairns (who&amp;rsquo;s into the DJ Steveboy stuff) says there are no VERBAL cues to change from walking to running - but a very noticeable musical cue &amp;hellip; and the bpm changing from an obvious jogging speed to an obvious walking one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;phedippidations-the-c25k-episode-http-steverunner-blogspot-com-podcasts-fdip86-mp3:490078144366c347e8b62bdc4bb6103e&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://steverunner.blogspot.com/PodCasts/Fdip86.mp3&#34;&gt;Phedippidations: The C25K Episode&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Listen to Steve Runner, the high priest of running Podcasters talk about the Couch to 5k program. A great background in C25K.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;put this stuff to sound cloud?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>